Curriculum Vitae

My name is Samuele.

I'm an Italian spatial data scientist passionate about GIS & programming, with acquired experience in data collection, analysis and visualization. Currently, I work at Eurac Research providing scientific consultancy to public authorities in the field of urban and regional planning for the clean energy transition.

My focus is on developing spatial decision support system tools to assist local administrations in reaching climate neutrality goals.

The best way to get a hold of me is via email: samuelezilio95@gmail.com.

You can also find me on GitHub: https://github.com/samuzilio.

Work Experience

06/2024 - Ongoing

Researcher

Eurac Research, Bolzano (Italy)

05/2021 - 05/2024

Junior Researcher

Eurac Research, Bolzano (Italy)

09/2020 - 04/2021

Trainee

Eurac Research, Bolzano (Italy)

Education

2017 - 2020

MSc in Planning and Policies for Cities, Environment and Landscape

 $\operatorname{IUAV},$ Venice (Italy) + Universidade de Lisboa, Lisbon (Portugal)

2014 - 2017

BSc in Urban and Regional Planning

IUAV, Venice (Italy) + İstanbul Teknik Üniversitesi, Istanbul (Turkey)